<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Hiro Yamakawa</title>
    <link>http://yamhiroto.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Hiro Yamakawa</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://yamhiroto.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2023 wrap up </title>
      <link>http://yamhiroto.github.io/posts/2023-wrap-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://yamhiroto.github.io/posts/2023-wrap-up/</guid>
      <description>Here is a quick summary of what I achieved in 2023, what I&amp;rsquo;ve learned from it and my 2024 goals. Overall very happy with this year !&#xA;Successes Personal I&amp;rsquo;ve moved back to Helsinki in Feb 2023 after spending 5 months in Antwerp (Belgium). It was a fun experience, I will miss the cheap beers and the good fries ( Get drunk and filled for a tenner, unbeatable) . The Brick was a blast, joined it 3 days after I moved to Antwerp and would DEFINITELY recommend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024 targets</title>
      <link>http://yamhiroto.github.io/posts/targets-for-2024./</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://yamhiroto.github.io/posts/targets-for-2024./</guid>
      <description>Realistic goals I set myself for this year. Remember, Good thing takes time.&#xA;Work - Hard skill Complete the JAVA Mooc from Helsinki University (soon, currently part 10) Read Design Data Intensive Applications and Data Engineering Fundamentals Complete CS61b Complete Neetcode 75 Get better at System design Work on my poker face Personal Get my driving license (I know I know) Get 15 levels of wanikani. 20 ambitious. Roughly 20 days / level 10 session of meditation / month 1 blog every 2 months 0 cig.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Useful Tech resources</title>
      <link>http://yamhiroto.github.io/posts/useful-tech-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://yamhiroto.github.io/posts/useful-tech-resources/</guid>
      <description>There was an older version of this post previously available on this blog, but I wasn&amp;rsquo;t satisfied with it as it was becoming a mess.&#xA;I have decided to only list the websites here that I have personally used, enjoyed, and would recommend to others in real life (IRL).&#xA;You just got started SQL SQLZoo: The website I usually advise to friends or colleagues who are getting started with SQL. You should become comfortable with any of those exercises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why this blog</title>
      <link>http://yamhiroto.github.io/posts/why-this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://yamhiroto.github.io/posts/why-this-blog/</guid>
      <description>Why this blog You certainly ended up here while casually &amp;ndash;stalking&amp;ndash; browsing my LinkedIn page, and you might be wondering what&amp;rsquo;s in store.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;ve always had the idea of starting a blog for a few reasons:&#xA;Firstly, I thought it would be enjoyable. Similar to you, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot happening in my mind, and I want to keep my thoughts organized on certain subjects. Recognizing that I&amp;rsquo;ve amassed a significant collection of web resources, I felt it was time to start organizing them.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
