<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Hiro Yamakawa</title>
    <link>http://yamhiroto.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Hiro Yamakawa</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://yamhiroto.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Interesting posts</title>
      <link>http://yamhiroto.github.io/posts/interesting-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yamhiroto.github.io/posts/interesting-posts/</guid>
      <description>SWE Career     A year ago I graduated from a bootcamp with 21 other people. Only 6 of us are working as SWEs today - Reddit  Japan     Tokyo Replica Food - NYTimes Magazine  Entrepreneurship     Starter Story: Learn how people are starting successful businesses  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful Tech resources</title>
      <link>http://yamhiroto.github.io/posts/useful-tech-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yamhiroto.github.io/posts/useful-tech-resources/</guid>
      <description>SQL     SQLZoo: The one I usually advise to friends who get started with SQL Selectstarsql SQL Murder Mystery: quick murder investigation using SQL, this one is rather fun SQLbolt BIPP.io A Curious Moon - Big Machine: Learn PostgreSQL the way the pros do: on the job and under pressure 🌔 🚀 Medium-hard SQL interview Questions - HN Stratascratch SQL questions Leetcode Top 70 :requires Premium Leetcode account How does Database indexing work - HN  Tools     The Missing Semester of Your CS Education GIT immersion  Python     Jetbrains Academy / Hyperskill : Paid Courses / tight integration with PyCharm IDE The little book of Python Anti Patterns : How not to write Python Code Python builtins worth learning Understanding all of Python, through its builtins Python Design Patterns - HN Python Morsels: Free Trials / Write better Python code in 30 min each Week  Computer Science     Teach Yourself CS Arcane Algorithm Archive  Data Engineering     How Data Engineering Works - Youtube Data Engineering Wiki  BackEnd     Backend Developer Roadmap : Check the other roadmaps and guides !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful Websites, Apps and Accessories</title>
      <link>http://yamhiroto.github.io/posts/useful-websites/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yamhiroto.github.io/posts/useful-websites/</guid>
      <description>Websites    - [YOPMAIL](https://yopmail.com) : A disposable mail address (to keep your main one clean from any spams - [MULLVAD](https://mullvad.net/) : Useful VPN, also available on Smartphones and tablets (5e/Month) - [MINE](https://saymine.com/): to request deletion of personal data from websites  More TBA
Chrome Extension    - [Toby](https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/toby-for-chrome/hddnkoipeenegfoeaoibdmnaalmgkpip): Tab organizer - [Ublock origin](https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/ublock-origin/cjpalhdlnbpafiamejdnhcphjbkeiagm): to block ads(instead of Adblock) - [Block Site](https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/block-site-website-blocke/eiimnmioipafcokbfikbljfdeojpcgbh): to be more productive - [Grammarly](https://chrome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why this blog</title>
      <link>http://yamhiroto.github.io/posts/why-this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yamhiroto.github.io/posts/why-this-blog/</guid>
      <description>Why this blog    You certainly ended up here while casually &amp;ndash;stalking&amp;ndash; checking my Linkedin Page and might be wondering what you will find here.
I always wanted to start a blog for several reasons:
 I thought it would be fun Like you, a lot is going on up there and I want to keep my thoughts clear and organized on some subjects. I realized I had gathered a significant amount of web resources and I wanted to start organizing them: if they are not worth sharing, they are not worth keeping I &amp;ldquo;bombed&amp;rdquo; my first carrier in my early years (I am not that old) and I want to share all the lessons learned I wish someone had told me when I first graduated I want to be able to share a page on my subjects of interest with like-minded people and maybe start interesting (non/for-profit) projects together!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
